Guide to the Stanford University, Vice President for Business Affairs, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Dermatology Expansion - Disbursements, 1968-1972 (Box 112, Folder 1)
- Dermatology Expansion - Exhibits, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 7)
- Dermatology Expansion - Legal, 1969-1972 (Box 111, Folder 33)
- Dermatology Expansion - No. 1 - Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 112, Folder 3)
- Dermatology Expansion - No. 2 - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 112, Folder 4)
- Dermatology Expansion - Supplements, Change Orders, 1969-1970 (Box 112, Folder 2)
- Dermatology Expansion II - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 112, Folder 6)
- Dermatology Expansion II - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 5)
- Dermatology Remodeling - Legal Documents, 407, 1963-1964 (Box 102, Folder 2)
- Design Guidelines, 1972-1974 (Box 33, Folder 45)
- Deutsch, J. Anthony, 1959-1965 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Development Office, see: General Secretary, 1960-1965 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Dewey Enterprises, Inc. (Gem Shoe Repair) - Correspondence, 1958-1967 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Dils, Eugene W. & Frances L., 1950-1958 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Dinkelspiel Auditorium, for construction of bldg see: Music Bldlg., 1958-1970 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- D'Ambrogio Legal Action: H.L. Price et all v. Behavioral Sciences Inst. (BSI) and Stanford University #2, 1973-1974 (Box 69, Folder 15)
- D'Ambrogio Legal Action: H.L. Price et all v. Behavioral Sciences Inst. (BSI) and Stanford University #1, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 16)
- Doane, Mrs. R. W., 1932-1959 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Dogs On Campus, 1951-1971 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Dolores - 774 - University Owned, 1958-1965 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Dormitories - Casa Ventura, 1941-1953 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Dormitories - Crothers Hall - Furniture & Equipment, 1947-1954 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Dormitories - Encina Rehabilitation, 1942-1956 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Dormitories - Madrono Hall, 1950-1958 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Dormitories - Sequoia Hall, 1942-1954 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Dormitories - Studies on, 1941-1952 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Dormitories - Union Unit, 1933-1959 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Dormitories & Dining Halls - Tax Matters, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Dougall, Herbert E., 1946-1958 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Downtown Palo Alto, Inc., 1959-1972 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Draper, Gaither & Anderson, see: Welch Road Investment Company (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Drexler, Mrs. Elsie - Drexler Hall, 1930-1939 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Durand, Wm. F., 1935-1951 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- DuShane, Graham P., 1946-1956 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Dyment, Bertha S., 1930-1954 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- E. R. L. [Electronics Research Laboratory] Alterations- Legal Documents, 1963-1964 (Box 101, Folder 26)
- Earth Sciences Bldg. - Contract Changes, 164, 1968-1971 (Box 107, Folder 4)
- Earth Sciences Bldg. - Disbursements, 164, 1961-1970 (Box 107, Folder 2)
- Earth Sciences Bldg. - Disbursements, File No. 2, 1970-1974 (Box 107, Folder 1)
- Earth Sciences Bldg. - Exhibits (Box 107, Folder 15)
- Earth Sciences Bldg. - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, File 1, 1968-1969 (Box 107, Folder 14)
- Earth Sciences Bldg. - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, File 2, 1969-1970 (Box 107, Folder 13)
- Earth Sciences Bldg. - General Correspondence, #I, 1960-1968 (Box 107, Folder 12)
- Earth Sciences Bldg. - General Correspondence, #II, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 11)
- Earth Sciences Bldg. - General Correspondence, #III, 1970-1971 (Box 107, Folder 10)
- Earth Sciences Bldg. - Grant & Addendum, 1967-1969 (Box 107, Folder 7)
- Earth Sciences Bldg. - Legal, 164, 1961-1971 (Box 107, Folder 3)
- Earth Sciences Bldg. - Supplements, File I, No 1-33r, 1968-1969 (Box 107, Folder 5)
- Earth Sciences Bldg. - Supplemets, File II, No 34-92, 1969-1971 (Box 107, Folder 6)
- Earth Sciences Bldg. - Testing Lab Reports, File I, 1966-1969 (Box 107, Folder 9)
- Earth Sciences Bldg. - Testing Lab Reports, File II, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 8)
- East Bayshore Community Comprehensive Planning Program, 1971-1974 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Eating Clubs - El Toro, 1935-1959 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Eating Clubs - General and InterClub Council, #1, 1944-1958 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Eating Clubs - General and InterClub Council, #2, 1958-1965 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Eating Clubs - General and Interclub Council, #3, 1957-1976 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Eating Clubs - Interclub Advisory Board, 1951-1975 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Eating Clubs - Quarterly Reports, 1958-1967 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Eating Clubs - Sequoia Trust & Rental Agmt., 1942-1951 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Effect of Stanford University on the Local Housing Market, The. Patricia Ann Wilson, Econ 199, June 6, 1969 (Binder) (Box 95)
- Egbert, Peter R., 1974-1979 (Box 73, Folder 24)
- Eichler, Joseph, 1954-1956 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Eisen, Samuel K., 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- El Escarpado, 445 (University Owned), 1933-1959 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Electric Plant Improvements, 1965-1967 (Box 101, Folder 31)
- Elevator - Otis, 704, File III, 1972 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- Eliel, Paul, 1936-1945 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Elliott, Mrs. Ellen Coit, 1934-1957 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Ely, Leonard (Leonard Ely Company, Used Car Lot), 1958-1962 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Emerson, Prof. James G., 1924-1946 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Encina Administrative Offices Relocation, 791, 1973-1975 (Box 109, Folder 17)
- Encina Barber Shop, Kenneth Dzerigian, Lessee, 1954-1967 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Encina Center Fire Sprinkler Specs, 833 (Box 109, Folder 9)
- Encina Center Wing Basement - Rm 10-10A, 30 Alterations for ADP, Rm 51-55, Alterations for Facilities, 1973-1974 (Box 104, Folder 2)
- Encina Center Wing Restoration - Carpet Replacement, 704, File IX, 1972-1973 (Box 105, Folder 7)
- Encina Center Wing Restoration - Costs, & Budget, General Administration, 704, File VI, 1972-1974 (Box 105, Folder 4)
- Encina Center Wing Restoration - Fire Sprinklers and Fire Alarm, 704, File VII, 1972-1974 (Box 105, Folder 5)
- Encina Center Wing Restoration - Paint & Plaster Repair & Alternate 4th Flr. 593B, 704, File VIII, 1972-1973 (Box 105, Folder 6)
- Encina Center Wing Restoration, File II - Construction, Williams & Burrows, 704, 1972-1973 (Box 104, Folder 17)
- Encina Center Wing Restoration, File I - Design, 704, 1972-1973 (Box 104, Folder 16)
- Encina Coffee Shop - Planning, 1965-1969 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Encina East - Fire Loss, 1972 (Box 108, Folder 16)
- Encina East Wing Basement - Air Conditioning (Health Physics), 690, 1972-1975 (Box 103, Folder 18)
- Encina Hall - Center Wing Attic, #502, 1972-1973 (Box 108, Folder 8)
- Encina Hall - Changes 1962, 1963, 1964, 1965, 1969, 1970 and Future Plans (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Encina Hall - Renovations Rooms 10 & 30 (Box 108, Folder 17)
- Encina Hall Storage Rooms, Third, fourth and fifth floors, 1958, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Encina Room 100 - Alterations for “General Accounting” and “Funds”, 671, 1972-1973 (Box 103, Folder 38)
- Encina West Wing - Correspondence, File III, 1970-1971 (Box 108, Folder 13)
- Encina West Wing - Record of Employee Interview - HEW, 1968-1969 (Box 108, Folder 9)
- Encina West Wing - Supplements, 1968-1969 (Box 108, Folder 4)
- Encina West Wing (Food Research) - Contract Changes, 1968-1970 (Box 108, Folder 3)
- Encina West Wing (Food Research) - Correspondence, File I, 1965-1968 (Box 108, Folder 15)
- Encina West Wing (Food Research) - Correspondence, File II, 1968-1969 (Box 108, Folder 14)
- Encina West Wing (Food Research) - Disbursement, #389, 1966-1972 (Box 108, Folder 1)
- Encina West Wing (Food Research) - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports & Architect’s Reports to HEW, File I, 1968-1969 (Box 108, Folder 12)
- Encina West Wing (Food Research) - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, File II, 1969 (Box 108, Folder 11)
- Encina West Wing (Food Research) - Grants, 1967 (Box 108, Folder 10)
- Encina West Wing (Food Research) - Legal 1965-1975 (Box 108, Folder 2)
- Encina West Wing (Food Research) - Testing Lab Reports, File II, 1969 (Box 108, Folder 5)
- Encina West Wing (Food Research) -Testing Lab Reports, File I, 1968-1969 (Box 108, Folder 6)
- Encina West Wing Remodel - Affirmative Action Program Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 108, Folder 7)
- Energy Conservation in Existing Buildings - Center for Biological Sciences, Herrin Building, 1976 (Binder) (Box 35)
- Energy Conservation in Existing Buildings - Earth Sciences, Mitchell Building, 1976 (Binder) (Box 35)
- Energy Conservation in Existing Buildings - Graduate School of Business, 1976 (Binder) (Box 35)
- Energy Conservation in Existing Buildings - Space Engineering, Durand Building, 1976 (Binder) (Box 35)
- Energy Crisis, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Energy Management and Conservation Program, 1977 (Binder) (Box 35)
- Energy Performance File, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 40)
- Energy Study, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 38)
- Energy, 1974-1976 (Box 33, Folder 37)
- Environmental Impact Report, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Erwin, E. S., 1935-1968 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Escondido Road, 865, 1924-1967 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Escondido Village - Counter Delaminations - Williams & Burrows, 1961-1963 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Escondido Village - Electrical Service, 1963-1965 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Escondido Village - Photos, 1960-1962 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Escondido Village - Single Student Apts., 1963-1967 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Escondido Village III - Legal Documents, #321, 1963-1969 (Box 101, Folder 28)
- Escondido Village Paving Repairs, 709, 1972 (Box 109, Folder 23)
- Escondido Village V - Budget and Fiscal, 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Escondido Village V - Bulletins, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Escondido Village V - Contract Changes, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Escondido Village V - Correspondence #1, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Escondido Village V - Correspondence #2, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Escondido Village V - Correspondence #3, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Escondido Village V - Correspondence #4, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Escondido Village V - DHUD [Department of Housing and Urban Development] Requirements, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Escondido Village V - Disbursements, File #1, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Escondido Village V - Disbursements, File #2, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Escondido Village V - Exhibits (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Escondido Village V - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, File #1, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Escondido Village V - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, File #2, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Escondido Village V - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, File #3, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Escondido Village V - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, File #4, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Escondido Village V - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, File #5, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Escondido Village V - Field Orders & Supplements, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Escondido Village V - Insurance Register, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Escondido Village V - Legal II, 604, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Escondido Village V - Legal, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Escondido Village V - Multipurpose Facility - ‘Payrolls’, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Escondido Village V - Multipurpose Facility - Affirmative Action Program, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Escondido Village V - Multipurpose Facility - Affirmative Action Report, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Escondido Village V - Multipurpose Facility - Budget & Fiscal, 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Escondido Village V - Multipurpose Facility - Bulletins & Supplements, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Escondido Village V - Multipurpose Facility - Contract Changes, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Escondido Village V - Multipurpose Facility - Disbursements, 1971-1975 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Escondido Village V - Multipurpose Facility - Exhibits (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Escondido Village V - Multipurpose Facility - Field Inspector’s Progress Report, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Escondido Village V - Multipurpose Facility - General Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Escondido Village V - Multipurpose Facility - Legal, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Escondido Village V - Testing Laboratory Rpts, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Escondido Village, 1, 1959-1964 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Escondido, 510 - Alvarado Hall, 1935-1939 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Escondido, 859, 1936-1968 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Escondido, 860 (Tower House), 1935-1962 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Espinosa, A. M. & M. G., 1927-1959 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Espinosa, Aurelio M., Jr. - 572 Lausen, 1952-1959 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Esslinger, Arthur A. & Mary Agnes, 1941-1946 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Executive Order 11615 (Wage, Price freeze), 1971 (Box 73, Folder 22)
- Facilities & Properties, 1972-1974 (Box 100, Folder 5)
- Faculty Club Bar Remodeling, (928), 1974-1975 (Box 108, Folder 20)
- Faculty Club, 1934-1963 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Faculty Study Additions - Legal Documents, 1962-1964 (Box 101, Folder 25)
- Faculty/Staff Housing - Time Management, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 17)
- Faculty/Staff Housing, 1971-1975 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- Fairchild Aerial Surveys, Inc., 1951-1956 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Fairvale Investments - Site Improvements, 1961-1962 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Farmer, Edward M., 1949-1964 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Faust, Clarence H. & Gladys L., 1947-1951 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Feigenbaum, Edward A., 1961-1967 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Felt Lake - Damage to Flume, 1950-1955 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Festinger, Leon, 1960-1967 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Field, Professor John, 1931-1955 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- Finance, general, 1973-1974 (Box 99, Folder 19)
- Financial Aids Office - Work Study Program, #1, 1965-1967 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- Financial Aids Office - Work Study Program, #2, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Financial Aids Office - Work Study Program, #3, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Financial Aids Office - Work Study Program, #4, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Financial Aids Office - Work Study Program, #5, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Financial Aids Office - Work Study Program,#6, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Financial Data & Related Correspondence - Frenchman’s Terrace, 1970-1976 (Box 95, Folder 16)
- Finch Volney C. & Frances B., 1936-1954 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Finch, Mrs. Frances B., 1953-1966 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Finch, Nathan C., 1965 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Fire and Police Station - Legal, 1966-1968 (Box 101, Folder 24)
- Fire Department, 1962-1963 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Fire Department, 1963-1965 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Fire House - Proposed, 1956-1966 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Fire Sprinkler Systems, Knoll, File 1, 832, 1973-1975 (Box 109, Folder 10)
- Fire Sprinkler Systems, Memorial Church, File 1, 828, 1973-1975 (Box 109, Folder 13)
- Fire Sprinkler Systems, School of Education, File 1, 831, 1973-1975 (Box 109, Folder 11)
- Fire Sprinkler Systems, Student Services Bldg. (Old Union), File 1, 829, 1973-1975 (Box 109, Folder 12)
- Fisher, Anne B., Estate of, 1963-1972 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Fitch, Mrs. Margaret C., 1961-1968 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Fitch, Thomas B., 1953-1959 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Flags on Campus, 1952-1966 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- FLEET (Florida Lifecycle Energy Evaluation Technique Manual) (Binder) (Box 35)
- Flight Training - Air Force, 1963-1964 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Flight Training - Army, 1964-1966 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Flight Training - Navy, 1963-1969 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Florida Energy Conservation Manual, 1975 (Binder) (Box 35)
- Florida Life Cycle Analysis Manual, 1975 (Binder) (Box 35)
- Food Service - Arthur W. Dana, Consultant, 1962-1969 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Food Service - Building (Program &Design), 1967 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Food Service - Contract Service and Kitchen Consultants, 1962-1968 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Food Service - Employee Housing, 1955-1964 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Food Service - Encina, 1965-1968 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Food Service - General, 1960-1966 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Food Service - Guest Meals, Transfers & Exchanges, 1961-1970 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Food Service - History, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Food Service - Moore, 1955-1963 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Food Service - Stern, 1949-1966 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Food Service - Wilbur, 1955-1966 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Foothill Lots Available, 1955-1956 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Foothills Development - Non-University, 1965-1971 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Foothills Environmental Design Study - Exhibits, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Foothills Environmental Design Study (by Livingston & Blayney for Palo Alto), 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Foothills Environmental Design Study (by Livingston & Blayney for Palo Alto), 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Forsberg, John E., 1959-1966 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Forstman, H. Jackson, 1962-1964 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Founding Grant - and General Information, see also: “Founding Grant” Folder 2, 1908-1957 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Fowler, Roy M. (Union Barber Shop), 1953-1962 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- FPC&U Projects - Engineering Building, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 48)
- Frankel, Hermann F. and Lilli, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Frankel, Theodore T., 1960-1963 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Fraternities - Financial Reports, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Fraternities #2 - Misc., 1958-1965 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- Fraternities and Sororities - General, 1919-1944 (Box 34, Folder 29)
- Fraternities at Stanford ( brochure) (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Fraternities, 1927-1938 (Box 34, Folder 30)
- Fraternity Cluster III - Changes to Contract, 1967-1969 (Box 102, Folder 4)
- Fraternity Cluster III - Grants, HUD Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 102, Folder 3)
- Fraternity Cluster III - Legal, File 2 (Box 102, Folder 18)
- Fraternity Cluster III, File I - Legal Documents, 1963-1968 (Box 103, Folder 8)
- Fraternity Contract, 1945-1948 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Fraternity Contract, 1943-1945 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- Fraternity House Survey - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Fraternity House Survey, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- Fraternity Housing, 1928-1940 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Fraternity Moratorium, 1944-1945 (Box 34, Folder 28)
- Frenchman's Hill - Bulletins, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 18)
- Frenchman's Hill - Community T.V., 1966-1969 (Box 73, Folder 27)
- Frenchman's Hill - Correspondence (Research Park Lessees), 1967 (Box 73, Folder 19)
- Frenchman's Hill and Bowdoin Street Completion - Legal, 1966-1970 (Box 101, Folder 29)
- Frenchman's Terrace, 1975-1976 (Box 95, Folder 13)
- Frost Amphhitheater - including Construction, #1, 1949-1964 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Frost Amphitheater (including construction), No. II, 1965-1971 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Fuel: Rates & Consumption, 1974-1976 (Box 33, Folder 39)
- Fuhrman, Frederick A., 1952-1968 (Box 34, Folder 31)
- Furnishings for Construction Projects - Biological Sciences Building, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Furnishings for Construction Projects - Chemical Engineering, 1964-1966 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Furnishings for Construction Projects - Cowell Student Health Center (including kitchen equipment),1964-1967 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Furnishings for Construction Projects - Faculty Club, 1962-1966 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Furnishings for Construction Projects - General, 1964-1966 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Furnishings for Construction Projects - Graduate School of Business, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Furnishings for Construction Projects - Old Union, Student Services Bldg., 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Furnishings for Construction Projects - Undergraduate Library, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- G. P. I. Meeting, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 31)
- G. P. I., 1974-1977 (Box 33, Folder 32)
- Galantine, Joseph #2, 1955-1965 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Gallenkamp Stores, Co. - Correspondence, Lease, 1955-1965 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Gambetta, Louis, Jr., 1941-1960 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Game Refuge, 1921-1954 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Garbage - Regulations, etc., 1934-1956 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Garrett, Sylvester, 1949-1953 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Garrett, Verne F. - Motor Sales, 1954-1961 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Garriot, Owen K., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Garst, Johnathan, 1940-1944 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- General - Frenchman’s Terrace, 1970-1974 (Box 95, Folder 17)
- General Electric Fellowship, 1956-1960 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- General Electric Laboratory - Light Military Electronics Equipment Department, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- General Electric Microwave Laboratory - Unit No. 1 - Contract & Minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- General Electric Microwave Laboratory - Unit No. 1 -Correspondence, Folder 1, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- General Secretary (and Secretary to the University) #1, 1953-1969 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Geology Corner - Access to Fans, 837, 1973-1975 (Box 103, Folder 25)
- Gerona Road - 440 (University Owned), 1934-1962 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Gibbons, James F., 1968 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Gicovate, Bernard, 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Gifts - Policies & Procedures - 1947-1966 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Gifts Miscellaneous - #1 ro R. H. Anderson, Amber Oil, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Gifts Miscellaneous - Art Works, Gift Deeds, Doc. #1596, 1963-1968 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Gifts Miscellaneous - Est. of Lorenzo Besio, Promissory Notes, 1960-1975 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Gifts Miscellaneous - General, A - L, 1962-1971 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Gifts Miscellaneous - General, M - Z, 1960-1976 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Gifts Miscellaneous - Hewlett-Packard Stock, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Gifts Miscellaneous - Hickey (Dummy File) 1974 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Gifts Miscellaneous - Hickey, Catherine Ewell McArthur, 1963-1974 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Gifts Miscellaneous - Huntsinger, Fritz - stock in Vetco Offshore Industries, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Gifts, Misc. - Suinn, Richard M. and Dauterman, Wm. L. - Publications Royalties, 1967-1969 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Gifts, Misc. - Ward, Eugene V. - Quitclaim Deed 627 Salvatierra, Stanford, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Ashton, Nina, 1961-1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Carter, Robert B., 1964 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Childs, LeRoy (Pottery Shack, Laguna Beach, Calif., 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Dungan, John A., 1962-1965 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Heraty Organization “Gloria J.” Yacht, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Hummel, Donald M. Credit Bureau Stock - Correspondence, #2, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Hummel, Donald M. Credit Bureau Stock - Exhibits (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Hummel, Donald M. Credit Bureau Stock, #1, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Ilderton, David, Boat to Sailing Assn., Doc. #1767, 1968-1972 (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Jergins, Diane B., 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Jergins, Dorothy M., 1964 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Neill & Co., Inc. - Airplane, Document 1280, 1962-1965 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Petrini, James, 1962-1969 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Reis, William D., Santa Margarita Ranch, Exhibits - General III, Materials Received from Santa Margarita Land and Cattle Co. files, 1957-1965 (Box 72, Folder 12)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Reis, William D., Santa Margarita Ranch, Exhibits - General I, 1970-1973 (Box 72, Folder 15)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Reis, William D., Santa Margarita Ranch, Exhibits - General II, 1971-1974 (Box 72, Folder 21)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Reis, William D., Santa Margarita Ranch, Exhibits - Mineral Rights, 1965-1972 (Box 72, Folder 20)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Reis, William D., Santa Margarita Ranch, Exhibits - Water, 1963-1972 (Box 72, Folder 19)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Reis, William D., Santa Margarita Ranch, General I, 1962-1971 (Box 72, Folder 14)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Reis, William D., Santa Margarita Ranch, Inquiries, 1971-1973 (Box 72, Folder 18)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Reis, William D., Santa Margarita Ranch, Santa Margarita Land and Cattle Co. - Minutes and Financial Reports, 1971-1974 (Box 72, Folder 17)